Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/wolfgangakohl (Linkedln)

Top Skills

Problem Solving Teamwork

Communication

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Limited Working)

Honors-Awards

Credits Speaker

Panel Commentator

Regional Developer

Trainer

Wolfgang K.

MBA Candidate at Cornell Johnson | Ex-Activision Blizzard | Finance, Investments, Modeling, Analysis, Emerging Markets, Data Science, Gaming, TMT

New York, New York, United States

Summary

As a fund manager at The Cayuga Fund, I apply my data analytics and business strategy skills to manage a student-run investment fund for Cornell's endowment. I am also a student fellow at Cornell Emerging Markets Institute, where I conduct research on the role of emerging markets in the global economy. Additionally, I was a summer associate at Azaí Consultores, a leading consulting firm in Latin America, where I worked on business development, pricing strategies, and project management. I am currently pursuing an MBA degree at Cornell Johnson Graduate School of Management, with a focus on finance and emerging markets. I have a BS degree in Business Administration and Management Information Systems from Fowler College of Business at San Diego State University. I have over seven years of experience as a senior data scientist and business strategist at Blizzard Entertainment, where I contributed to the development and success of multiple data products and games, such as World of Warcraft, Hearthstone, and Starcraft 2. I am passionate about using data and technology to create value and impact in the world of finance, gaming, and entertainment.

Experience

The Cayuga Fund Fund Manager May 2023 - Present (7 months) Ithaca, New York, United States

Student run investment fund for Cornell's endowment

Quantitative and fundamental research / analysis, emphasis on primary research / sources

Consumer sector with sub-sector coverage of Movies/Entertainment - Theme Parks

Cornell Emerging Markets Institute

Student Fellow May 2023 - Present (7 months) Ithaca, New York, United States

Premier research center on the role of emerging markets in the global economy

Interest in multi-class foreign investment, main interest in Real Estate

Azaí Consultores Summer Associate June 2023 - August 2023 (3 months) Bogota, D.C., Capital District, Colombia

Business development - growth strategy
Pricing strategies
Project management

Blizzard Entertainment Lead Data Scientist / Business Strategy August 2015 - July 2022 (7 years) Irvine, CA

Technology and platform deployment strategies
Data standardization, training, and governance
Project / team management

Education

Cornell Johnson Graduate School of Management

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Finance, Real Estate · (2022 - 2024)

Fowler College of Business at San Diego State University
Bachelor of Science - BS, Business Administration (BSBA), Management
Information Systems · (2013 - 2015)